[ Pool Balls Clack ]
[ Door Opens ]
[ Charlie ]
♪ Come one, come all
to a beautiful show ♪
♪ It's gonna be awesome
and some other stuff ♪
♪ Dee-dee-dee-dee
do-dee-dee-dee
do-dee-dee-do-dee ♪
[ Laughs ]
♪ Some other musical stuff ♪♪
- What you doin', buddy?
- I wrote a musical.
Huh?
You wrote a musical?
Why? Why did you do that?
Uh, just to write a musical.
- Does there have to be
a reason? I don't think so.
- Yeah, there does.
Nobody writes a musical
for no reason.
It doesn't make sense.
All right. Well, this guy did.
So there you go.
[ Chuckles ]
- Who's the mark?
- What?
Oh.
Yeah.
No. There's no--
There's no mark, guys.
I wrote a musical.
It's pretty damn good, okay?
- I want to put it on.
- What's your angle?
- I don't have an angle.
- Whose face
are we shoving this in?
You don't shove a musical
in someone's face.
What are you talking about?
But who versus?
Who are we doing it versus?
Oh, my God. Are you guys
gonna make this about this?
I mean, look.
I just wrote a musical
to write a musical, okay?
I don't have
a ulterior motive here.
I'm not trying to
screw anyone or-or gain
anything out of it.
You know what? If you guys don't
want to be in it, I can find
other people to play your parts.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa.
Hang on there, pal.
Hang on. We're just
trying to wrap our heads
around this.
Yeah. I mean,
there's no reason to
give away our parts, okay?
All right.
No. We'll do it.
What's it called?
The Nightman Cometh.
♪
♪♪
Okay. Gather around,
please, everybody!
Uh, let's gather down front.
♪ I feel the magic
Do you feel the magic ♪
[ Chuckles ]
Here we go!
Now, you guys,
you all know Artemis.
Yes.
Uh, Artemis was kind enough...
to book for us
this fine local theater.
Okay. So, round of applause
for Artemis.
Very nice.
She also transcribed my work...
into a format
you might consider
a little bit more legible.
- Or literate.
She added words to it.
- All right.
No more interruptions now, Dee.
Thank you. Please.
Charlie, I got
a question for you.
Who's playing this Lead Boy?
That's gonna be Mac.
What?
Oh, yeah!
Lead, of course.
Who's playing the Dayman?
The Lead Boy becomes
the Dayman when he defeats
the Nightman. So it's also Mac.
Two parts?
Oh, yeah!
Wait. That's bullshit. Bro--
- The Nightman's a better role.
- He gets to play two roles?
Come on.
- It's the same person.
- Charlie, who's playing
the troll guy?
- You're gonna play
the troll guy.
- I'm the troll guy?
- Who else would be the troll?
- Oh! I like that.
All right. Good.
Can I do it naked?
Absolutely not.
Why would you want to be naked?
Because in the '70s,
everybody did theater naked.
Everybody got laid
all the time.
All right. This is not the '70s.
You're gonna do theater
with your clothes on, please.
Charlie, what the hell is this
play about? I'm a princess
who lives in a coffee shop?
You work in a coffee shop.
You don't live in a coffee shop.
Read closer.
Well, why am I in love
with a little boy?
You're in love with
a young man.
You wrote "boy."
All right. Well, man, boy--
it's a metaphor.
Well, the audience
is gonna think
I'm a child molester.
I've changed my mind.
I'm playing the Nightman.
What?
Whoa.
Yeah.
Why would you want to
play the Nightman?
The Nightman's badass, dude.
He has the eyes of a cat
and does karate
across the stage.
Where are you getting
that from? Karate?
I made that up.
It's gonna be great.
This is great.
That frees up Lead Boy
and Dayman.
I can play both.
I don't want you guys switching.
That's not how it works.
Frank, you got a guy
that does cat eyes?
I'm already on it.
Oh, my God.
For the love of God.
Uh, you know what?
Let's just get started.
[ Charlie ]
You guys ready?
[ Dennis ]
I'm ready.
[ Dee ] Yeah.
♪ Tiny boy
Little boy ♪
Ooh.
♪ Baby boy
I need you ♪
Ah. Ooh.
♪ Tiny boy, little boy ♪
♪ Want to make love
to you, boy ♪
♪ If you only knew ♪♪
Hold on a second.
Uh, Charlie.
- Yes.
- Are you goddamn kidding me?
What?
"Tiny boy, little boy,
baby boy"?
Yes?
You're wanting me to say
I want to make love
to a little baby tiny boy.
But I've explained this
to you, Dee. I'm talking
about the spirit of this man.
It's like a little boy.
It's a metaphor.
You keep using that word,
but I'm not convinced
you know what it means.
Also, I'm not making out
with Dennis later.
It says we're supposed to
at the end of the song.
That's not gonna happen.
I'm not sure I'm comfortable
with that either.
This is why I didn't
think you should be
playing the boy.
I don't want you guys
kissing either.
What if it's just...
a sexually
charged embrace?
Okay, Artemis,
please don't talk
to the talent.
You know what? Um--
All right. Screw this shit.
- If no one likes the song,
I'm gonna cut the song.
- Thank you.
No, no, no.
Don't cut the song, man.
I like the song.
Dee, apologize to Charlie.
I'm not gonna do that.
He wants me to bang this baby,
and I don't feel comfortable.
I think it's a bad idea
to cut the song, Charlie.
Thank you, Artemis.
Thank you very much.
All right.
Could you give me a second
with-with-with the talent here?
Thank you. Uh, Dennis,
could you take a five?
Uh, well,
I just don't want to
cut the song, man.
- I would like for you
to take a five.
- Five minutes?
Can we have five now, please?
Dee and I. Can I get--
Can you have a five over there?
Will you take a five, Dennis.
Take a five, please.
Yeah, I'll take a five.
[ Sighs ]
Okay, Dee.
The-The song is history.
Thank you, Charlie.
I appreciate that,
'cause I was uncomfortable.
Yeah, I bet.
What-What are we gonna sing
instead? What should I sing?
Uh, what's on
the back there?
It's the same song.
And what's on
the very back page?
Nothing.
Ah. Then that's what
you'll be singing.
Charlie,
this is my big song.
Yeah.
Everybody else has a big song.
I deserve to have one.
Do you?
Don't screw me like this,
Charlie. Come on.
Don't screw you?
Oh, I'm sorry, Dee.
Um, let me try
and remember something.
Uh, let's see. Was it--
Did Dee write a musical
and come to Charlie with it?
No! Charlie wrote a musical
and came to Dee with it--
and the gang.
And the gang likes to screw it
up and make it about themselves
and take it away from Charlie...
and ruin his
hopes and dreams.
So let me tell you something,
Dee. Let me break down
a scenario for you.
I could cut the song, okay?
Because I wrote it.
I could have Artemis
do the song, okay?
Because you did not write it.
Or I could strap on a wig
and I could do the song myself.
So you tell me,
Little Miss All That,
what do you want to do?
Song or no song?
Well, so-- song.
[ Gasps ]
Song?
Yeah. Song.
You want to sing a song.
I never wasn't gonna
sing the song.
You are excited
about singing a song,
and you want to sing a song.
Yeah. I would
like to do it.
Good!
Yeah, I'll--
So back up
on your podium you go.
Thank you.
Dennis, what are you doing?
I'm eating because
I'm very uncomfortable.
Well-- You guys are making--
Can you just get
on the stage, please?
And can we finish
this rehearsal?
It was really loud.
Don't start.
Technically, that
wasn't five minutes.
Okay. You know what?
You guys have me up to here.
Okay.
Okay, I'm here.
I don't want to
be here, okay?
Now I have to
play the piano,
and I'm all up here.
So let's--
You know what? Let's try
and get this down.
Let's try and work this
down a bit. Okay?
And you know
what's gonna do that?
Learning the song.
The way it's written.
Let's do it.
Back to the top.
Five, six,
seven, eight--
♪ Gotta pay the troll toll
to get into this boy's hole ♪
♪ You gotta pay the troll toll
to get in ♪
♪ You want this baby boy's hole
you gotta pay
the troll toll ♪♪
Stop, stop, stop.
All right. Um, not bad.
Good rhythm.
Love the enthusiasm. I feel
like you're saying "boy's hole."
And it's clearly "soul."
And I know-- Artemis, you did
write "soul," right?
I did write
"soul" definitely.
So it's "boy's soul."
♪ You gotta pay the troll toll
to get into this boy's hole ♪
♪ You gotta pay ♪♪
No, see? Right there.
It sounds like "hole."
Like, if you drag that--
Are you chewing gum?
Yeah.
Give me
the gum, okay?
G-Gi-- The gum, Frank.
Please.
He said no gum.
I said no gum, everyone.
[ Artemis ]
It's unprofessional.
Thank you.
Can I bring something up?
- Yes.
- Um, I think we have to be
very careful...
about how we do
the rape scene.
[ Dennis ] Yeah.
Well, what in God's name
are you talking?
There's no rape scene.
Well, sure.
Uh, I pay the troll toll,
and then I rape Dennis.
No. You don't rape him.
You become him.
You do not rape him.
[ Frank ]
He doesn't?
No.
Look. [ Sighs ]
Let me just walk you guys
through this, okay?
Here's what happens.
Yeah.
Once you've paid the toll--
I want you to come over
to Dennis, by his bed here.
I'll be lying back.
You want me to
cross the stage?
Yes.
All right. This is a great
opportunity to showcase some
skills and just put on a clinic.
I would rather you didn't.
I think the people
are gonna want to see that.
Let's not.
Then I'll hop up
sort of like a cat.
Like so. Meow.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Just leave it at that.
Okay. Once he gets near you,
you have to sense him, okay?
- Suddenly you sense him.
- What if I were to
position him...
in a way
where I get behind him,
then Frank could throw
that blanket he's got
right there over us.
Oh, yeah.
Then that way you can't
see the penetration.
That's a good idea. You know
what, Charlie? Because the
blanket will make the raping--
I'm sorry, the, uh,
"sexing" from behind--
feel more classy.
That's good. Then what
I can do is thrust this way.
And you can struggle.
Now I'm here. Okay?
I am--
I'm past where I thought
I could go. I'm like
all the way up here with it.
Oh, my God. Hey, you.
Oh, my God!
You scared me.
I'm sorry. I dropped,
like, a hundred dollar bill
under there,
can't find it anywhere,
and then-- What are you
doing walking here?
Is this one of
your walking places?
Charlie, I have Mace.
Oh, my God.
Check this out.
Uh, I have a free ticket
for you to see a musical
that I wrote.
Oh, wow!
A free ticket to a play
that I don't want to see.
You don't want to?
I don't.
It's a front row seat.
I don't care.
I don't want to see your play.
I'm gonna cut you a bargain.
Cut you a little deal.
Come see this play--
I didn't want to
have to do this,
but if you come see this play--
Yeah?
I'm gonna leave you alone
for the rest of your life.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay. So you're not gonna
follow me home anymore?
No.
And you're not gonna call me
at 3:00 in the morning--
No.
and tell me that
you are...
in the emergency room
in the hospital--
Yeah.
'cause you had a terrible
car accident.
Yeah. It's great that you came.
Well, you listed me
as your emergency contact.
Well, yeah.
Because I consider you that.
I have to go.
Look. Ah--
All right.
I swear to God,
I'm gonna leave you alone.
I'm gonna stop listing you
as my emergency contact.
I'm gonna stop calling you--
all that stuff--
if you see the musical.
That's how much
this means to me.
Nice.
Leave me alone.
You're not gonna regret it.
I regret it already.
All right.
♪♪ [ Whistling ]
[ Crowd Murmuring ]
[ Charlie Sighs ]
Oh, man.
What is going on?
When are we gonna start?
We're gonna start
when I'm ready.
Stop hounding me.
We were supposed to start
20 minutes ago.
We're not gonna start--
[ Gasps ] She's here!
She's here! She's here!
Who's here?
Circle in, everybody.
Can we get down in the middle.
Can we get down front.
Couple last-minute things.
I just want to brief
everyone on this.
Artemis,
can you bring in Gladys?
This is Gladys.
She's gonna be playing
the piano instead
of me tonight.
- What? Why?
- It's cool.
She knows all the songs.
Gladys, can you head out
and get us started?
I forgot to tell you.
Calvin Coolidge
was a good friend of mine.
You've been telling me that
Calvin Coolidge was a friend
of yours like all morning.
- How many times?
- Like a hundred times now.
Oh.
At a certain point,
I need you to stop...
telling the Calvin Coolidge
story and start playing--
Shh.
- Don't shush me.
Please don't shush me.
- Oh, my God, dude.
- Just get her out there
and get the play started.
- What the hell are you doing?
You can't be throwing us
curveballs like this.
I'm hanging on by a thread.
Don't argue with me now.
We just gotta do this.
Let's stick together.
Real quickly. A couple
things. I can't really
move my arms in this.
It is a rental.
I think I need to
rip the pit.
Do not rip that costume, okay?
It's very expensive.
Fine. But one other thing.
I wrote a song.
I'm gonna throw it in.
I swear to God,
you cannot add a song.
It's gonna happen.
I will smack your face--
off of your face.
Okay.
Do not add a song.
It's starting. Go.
You gotta get ready.
I'm not ready, dude.
I don't think I can do this.
Just get out there.
You're gonna be fine.
♪♪ [ Piano ]
[ Arguing ]
[ Charlie ]
Don't change your lines, okay?
Don't change your lines.
Do not rip that costume.
♪♪ [ Up-tempo Piano ]
What is this
strange feeling?
I feel so strange inside.
It's so strange,
but appealing.
I feel good. Ooh.
♪ Tiny boy ♪
♪ Little boy, baby boy
I need you ♪
Ah. Ooh.
Ah. Ooh. Oh.
♪ Tiny boy
Little boy ♪
♪ I want to touch you, boy ♪
♪ If you only knew ♪
♪ What I'd do to you ♪
♪ I need you, boy ♪
♪ If I was that boy
that's inside of you ♪
♪ Tiny boy, little boy
Baby boy ♪
Ah. Ooh.
♪ I need you
Tiny boy, little boy ♪
Ah. Ooh. Oh.
♪ Want to make love
to you, boy ♪
♪ If you only knew ♪
♪ What I'd do to you ♪
♪ Boy, oh, boy ♪
♪ If I was that boy
that's inside of you ♪
♪ Boy, oh, boy, oh, boy ♪
♪ Inside, inside
inside of you ♪
[ Together ]
♪ My boy ♪♪
[ Both Sigh ]
Oh, boy.
♪♪ [ Piano ]
[ Applause ]
♪ Just to be clear
I did not write that song ♪
♪ And have never had sex
with a child
Just to be clear ♪
♪ Just to be clear ♪
What--
What is happening?
♪ Most men find me to be
an eight or nine out of 10 ♪
♪ And I am available
to any interested men ♪
♪ Who'd like to get my number
after the show ♪♪
Keep singin', bitch.
You're not gonna have a face
by the time I'm done with you.
What the hell is she doing?
She's bombing like crazy.
What an idiot.
I was awesome though, right?
You? No, dude.
You totally froze up
out there. You sucked.
Um, I was hearing a lot
of laughs out there, bro.
Laughs are cheap.
[ Applause ]
I'm going for gasps.
Wait till you see, dude.
Gasps are where it's at.
I gotta go
pop my cat eyes in.
♪♪ [ Piano ]
[ Hisses ]
[ Laughing ]
We're getting a lot of laughs.
That's good.
That's not good.
This is not a comedy, okay?
No one's supposed
to be laughing.
♪♪ [ Snapping Rhythmically ]
You came at the right time.
Is he sleeping?
Yes. He's sleeping
right over there.
Just the way
you like 'em.
Did you bring the toll?
Confound your
lousy toll, troll.
[ Hisses ]
[ Laughing ]
Goddamn it.
Stop laughing at me.
♪ You gotta pay the troll toll
if you want to get into
that boy's hole ♪
♪ You gotta pay the troll toll
to get in ♪
♪ You want the baby boy's hole
you gotta pay
the troll toll ♪
♪ You gotta pay
the troll toll
to get in ♪
♪ Troll toll ♪
♪ What'd you say ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Troll toll ♪♪
Here's your toll, troll.
[ Coins Clink ]
Your boy awaits.
At last.
The boy's soul is mine.
[ Grunting ]
[ Chuckling ]
[ Snoring, Whistles ]
[ Gasps ]
Give me that leg, boy.
No.
[ Dennis ]
Dude, do you have
a boner right now?
[ Mac ]
Shut up, dude.
Don't ruin this for me.
[ Dennis ] What? What the hell
are you-- Jesus. Okay, stop.
[ Thumping ]
That's enough, dude.
Does it hurt?
Ow. Oh. God.
I am going to smack everyone
into tiny little pieces.
Hello, boy!
Come over here
and scratch my itchy-witchy
toesy-woesies.
No.
What?
- Get over here.
- No, Antonio.
I control you.
You control nothing.
I am not your
slave anymore,
and I am not a boy.
I am a man. See?
I was transformed...
by the strong,
musky power of true love.
I am now...
the Dayman.
- What the hell is that?
- You know what it is, bitch.
Bang!
[ Groans ]
Bang, bang,
bang, bang, bang!
[ Groaning ]
- ♪♪ [ Piano Tinkles Ominously ]
- [ Hisses ]
[ Audience Laughing ]
Where's the boy?
The boy is gone.
You can't tell me what to do.
N-- I didn't tell you what to--
You're skipping a line, dude.
Yeah. Uh--
You can't tell me what to do.
You're still skipping
the same line.
Just move past it...
'cause I can't remember--
God, it's crazy how much
better I am at acting than you.
I'm going to kick your ass, bro.
I'll tell you what.
I am the ruler of darkness.
I am the master of light.
I am the Dayman.
Whatever, bro.
Here's your whatever, bitch.
What? No, don't improv.
Don't tell me what to do.
[ Both Grunting ]
[ Groans ]
[ Shouts ]
[ Screams ]
Whoo!
[ Laughs ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Shouts ]
Body bag!
[ Groans ]
[ Growls ]
No.
Yes.
No!
[ Gasps ]
[ Exhales ]
♪♪ [ Piano Imitating Heartbeat ]
♪♪ [ Heartbeat Slows ]
[ Gasps, Groans ]
♪♪ [ Ends ]
[ Gasps ]
You have defeated the evil
that was here.
Naturally,
for I am the Dayman.
[ Gasps ] You once were a boy,
and now you are a man,
and I am in love with you.
That's right.
And now I am in love
with you.
♪ Dayman ♪
♪♪ [ Both Vocalizing ]
♪ Fighter of the Nightman ♪
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
♪ Champion of the sun ♪
♪ You're a master of karate
and friendship for everyone ♪
♪ Dayman ♪
♪ Dayman, Dayman
Dayman ♪
♪ Fighter of the Nightman ♪
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
♪ Champion of the sun ♪
♪ The sun, the sun, the sun ♪
♪ You're a master of karate
and friendship for everyone ♪
♪ Dayman ♪
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
♪ Fighter of the Nightman ♪
♪ Champion of the sun ♪
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
♪ You're a master of karate
and friendship for everyone ♪
♪ Dayman ♪♪
Stage freeze!
Don't say stage freeze.
Just do it.
♪♪ [ Vocalizing,
Voice Warbling ]
♪♪ [ Vocalizing Continues ]
♪ I was that little boy
That little baby boy was me ♪
♪ I once was a boy
but now I am a man ♪
♪ I fought the Nightman
lived as Dayman ♪
♪ Now I'm here
to ask for your hand ♪
♪ So if you want to marry, man
will you marry me ♪
♪ Will you come on stage
and join me ♪
♪ In this thing
called matrimony ♪
♪ Please say yes
and do not bone me ♪
♪ Please just marry ♪
♪ Me ♪♪
Is that it?
Uh-- Huh?
Is the play over?
Ye-- Yeah.
Okay. Great.
Well, then I'm out of here.
Hang on.
Hang on a second.
- Is it a yes, or--
- Is it a yes?
Really, Charlie? Will I marry
you? No. No, I will not.
I will never marry you.
And I also held up
my end of the bargain, so
I never have to see you again.
Okay. So wait. Just--
I'm sorry.
I want to get this clear.
Uh, you are saying no?
Oh, I am definitely,
definitely saying no.
Okay. Well, I didn't
ever sign anything.
So, um,
I'll see you tomorrow.
That's it.
You can go home.
It's over.
[ Dennis ]
Well, we're gonna do a bow.
Hold on.
Yeah?
Uh, if you want.
It was a great
musical, Charlie.
You did a great job.
She ain't worth it.
Told you nobody just writes
a musical for no reason.
I am here. I am--
I am past here.
And by the way,
I thought the rape scene
went really well.
I-- I am here.
I am here with it.
And that was awful for me.
And if you bring this up
back at the apartment tonight,
I am going to smack you.
I swear to God.
[ Voices Speaking Backwards ]